George, what sign are you?
George, 你是什么星座(sign)?
Virgo. September 19th, right?
处女座(Virgo) 9月19日, 对吗?
Yes.
是的
I don't know what time.
我不知道什么时间.
1:53 a.m. I was born in the middle of the night.
1:53a.m. 我是在大半夜出生的.
You're nice and hard-working.
你人很好并且非常勤奋.
You get along with Capricorns. Like Nina.
你和摩羯座(Capricorns)相处得很好. 比如Nina
Anne, how do you...
Anna, 你是如何...
January 7, 19...
1月7日, 19..
Uh-uh.
Prudent, raliable, artistic,...
谨慎的, 可靠地, 有艺术气息的...
What about me, Anne?
关于我呢, Anne?
You're dynamic, because you're a Leo.
你是有活力的, 因为你是一个狮子座(Leo)
And next August, You're "legal".
并且明年8月, 你就"合法了".
Huh?
I'm 21 on August 4th.
我21岁 在8月4日.
Since when do you have these strange powers?
自从何时, 你有这些奇异的能力?
I have no strange powers.
我没有奇异的能力
I have a photographic memory.
我有一个如照相机一般的记忆.
So?
So, I was personnel director for three years.
So, 我是人事主管 3年了.
And Dean, I hired you.
而Dean, 我雇佣了你.
Of course I know your birthdays!
我当然知道你的生日啦!